# Christopher Harris

- > Seeking front-end web development role
- Information Technology& Development

7 Poulter Street Hoppers Crossing Victoria 3029

0401717912 c.d.harris.dedoc@gmail.com https://bionic-fish.github.io

## **SUMMARY**

A tech savvy self-taught web developer who has a keen interest in learning, researching and developing new programming skills & concepts. Being a technology enthusiast & hobbyist, discovering, following & researching the latest trends, products and updates comes second nature. Having always had a solid interest in problem solving, evolving software integrations and a keen eye for design and implementation. These qualities provided with the accelerated rate in which software and tech are moving makes for an exciting career path as each day will bring forth a new emerging technology or challenge.

Since I am a self-taught programmer, I have no industry experience or working, collaborating and developing with a team. If applicable, I would very much be inclined to take on casual or weekend-based work in order to develop the skills necessary to provide value and perform at an industry level.

# **EXPERIENCE**

[November 2008 - January 2019]
[Currently Employed]
[Woolworths Ltd - MLDC Warehouse]

Casual Store person

## Responsibilities

- > Pick packing, manual handling and creating and completing store orders.
- > RFID scanning and accommodating WMS software to sort and store pallets.
- > Side-load & front load machinery for loading orders onto trucks for delivery.
- > Cycle Counts involve checking warehouse locations for discrepancies in number of products, resupply hold up and general flow of warehouse inventory.

[2018 - Current]
[Personal Projects]
[Web Development + Design Content]

Portfolio: https://bionic-fish.github.io

#### Design & Development

- > Semantic HTML5 elements. Latest CSS techniques, Grid + Flexbox layouts patterns
- > Responsive design layout for multiple devices and screen dimensions.
- > Adaptive grid & flex box elements for showcasing features + items
- > Utilizes the animated.js animation library as well as standard CSS and JavaScript animations.
- > Developed JavaScript for the Map API and display from Google Maps
- > Version control, hosting, site maintenance and debugging done with the aid of Github.

## **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

- > HTML5
- > CSS + Grid & Flexbox
- > JavaScript & jQuery
- > GitHub Version Control
- > Search Engine Optimization
- > Troubleshooting & Bug fixes
- > Building Templates

## PERSONAL SKILLS

- > Problem Solver
- > Creative Thinker
- > Adaptive & intuitive
- > Fast Learner
- > Approachable & Chill
- > Energetic & Hard Working

# **EDUCATION**

## [2015-2016]

## [RMIT School of Architecture, Melbourne City Campus]

# Advanced Diploma of Building Design [Arch]

## **Skills Acquired**

- > Adobe Photoshop
- > Autodesk AutoCad and Autodesk (acquired) Revit
- > Responsive design and layout techniques
- > Manual site planning and documentation
- > Pixel perfect design and attention to detail following specification and schematics
- > Design Mock-Ups & presentation techniques

## [Deferred, Transferred]

#### [2018-2019]

# [RMIT School of Business, Melbourne City Campus]

# Advanced Diploma of Information Technology

# **Skills Acquired**

- > Web Development: programming in HTML5, CSS and JavaScript
- > Database: MS Access, mySQL & mySQL server
- > Networking: CISCO networks & routing protocols, configuration & installation, administration & monitorization of networks.
- > OOP: object-oriented programming in Java utilizing the Oracle Java Development IDE.
- > Work Policy: research, evaluate and develop business reports & documentation attaining to specification and client requests. Implement database and technical solutions for business requirements

# [Completion in Sem 2, 2019]

## **REFERENCES**

References are available upon request.